[EP22]
Bring it here.
I know what's on it.
She chose to publish it at this time,
during the rotation of guards.
Very clever.
The journalists in Yang City should be rewarded.
Young Madam must have her reasons.
She must have been coerced by Chu Nanfeng.
She doesn't really want to divorce you.
That's good.
Deputy Li,
how long have you been with me?
Young Marshal,
7 years and 4 months.
Young Madam
is definitely not willing to do this.
I'm willing to lead the troops
to rescue her at night.
7 years and 4 months.
Do you remember
the tree my mother planted when she was a child?
Yes.
There are many gold bars
under the third brick beside the tree root.
Take them all.
Take your whole family
and leave Yang City to live a good life.
It's enough for you to live a lifetime.
The plague is rampant in the city.
Although our troops are damaged,
we are not powerless to fight
compared with Chu Nanfeng.
Young Marshal, you can't give up.
After the war,
the whole city will be damaged.
The people of Yang City will suffer.
Chu Nanfeng
just wants my power
and my life.
I'll give it to him.
I just hope the people of Yang City are safe.
Young Marshal,
you can't joke about your life.
What I want is for the people of Yang City
to live well.
You can go.
Get out.
You've been listening for so long.
Come down.
The show has just begun.
How could it be?
But at this time,
Young Marshal Ling
still believe
in so-called love.
You're so naive.
But...
Love...
I didn't expect
you to hide it so well.
You've got everyone fooled.
What's wrong with me?
I just want
to get everything I want.
and make my son
inherit everything of Ling family?
Am I wrong?
And you
got in my way,
got in my son's way.
You deserve to die.
You can take my life,
but Su Muwan is innocent.
Please let her go.
Beg me?
Fine.
On your knees.
Beg me.
Aren't you always above others?
Aren't you
the Young Marshal Ling?
On your knees.
Beg me.
Maybe
I'll consider
to let her go.
Beg me.
Please.
Let her go.
What a beautiful love story.
It's really
a rare
sunset scene.
It's just a pity.
Su Muwan
saw
what she shouldn't have seen.
She
must
die.
Die!
Kill me!
Kill me,
and Su Muwan
will
die immediately.
The people of Yang City
will also die.
What about Su Muwan?
What did you do to her?
Don't worry.
She is in a very safe place.
As long as you cooperate with me,
I won't hurt her.
How can you two
be together?
Running a shop on your own
is indeed more free.
But
it's good to have a powerful backer.
Mr. Chu can give me what I want.
Why wouldn't I cooperate with him?
You two have been colluding for a long time.
You know what?
I hate
the way you
pretend to be noble.
Your words
are really ridiculous.
Isn't it good to find a backer?
Pretending to be noble.
I really made a mistake about you.
I thought you had come around
and wanted to rely on yourself,
not on men.
You always
have a bad taste.
If Young Master Chu
didn't want to deal with you personally,
you would have been killed
for being such a nuisance.
Now,
he should be called General Governor Chu.
I'll leave her to you.
Don't forget what you promised me,
and the benefits you promised to Ye Family.
What do you want to do?
Xiao Wan,
Let's get married.
Marry me,
and you'll be the wife of the military governor,
far more prestigious
than the Young Marshal's wife.
Bastard!
Don't even think about it!
Ling Shenxing won't let you get away with this.
He will come to rescue me.
Ling Shenxing?
is disgraced
and imprisoned,
awaiting execution
at noon today.
Do you think
he'll come for you?
Marry me,
and I'll keep him alive
for one more day
for each day you're with me.
How's that?
Pretty good deal,
huh?